♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Oh, I love shopping
at Christmastime.
Ugh, mall food courts
are so depressing.
You can always tell
which fathers are disappointed
in their sons because they eat
lunch with their coats still on.
How's that food,
dum-dum?
Too bad eating
ain't math,
'cause then I'd have something
to be proud of.
I want to go
live with Mom.
I know. So do I.
Welcome to
Tommy Bahama.
Yeah, you got anything
for a poor fat person
who wants to look
like a rich fat person?
Of course.
Now, I'll mostly be
hitting on waitresses
who are too young and thin
to ever be interested in me.
Hitting on them in a
kindly, genial way?
No, in a threatening,
creepy,
I'm-joking-but-I'm-not-
really-joking way.
Y-You have anything
for that?
Sir, what you're describing is
precisely Mr. Bahama's vision.
ANNOUNCER: Tommy Bahama-- five
million uncles can't be wrong.
Hey, sorry to bother you,
but would you like to work here?
Me?
Yeah, you'd be perfect.
All right, now let me just take
off these security tags for you.
It's a living.
(Flintstones transition
music plays)
So random!
That's a comment on us.
Hey, check that out.
Oh, wow. This is awesome!
You know Jeff Garlin has
one of these in his house.
Ah, I love this chair.
Dog in a Jets jersey,
get in here!
God, I have the best basement.
Peter, this chair
costs $3,000.
That's not so
much, Lois.
It's only infinity times what
you bring home every week.
Peter, look over there.
Is that...
is that Jesus?
Whoa, yeah, wow.
It's been a while
since we've seen him.
Hey, Jesus!
Oh, hey, guys.
Hey, buddy.
What are you doing in Quahog?
Actually,
I never left.
Really?
Why didn't you call us?
Well, I felt kind of bad
about how we left things.
I wasn't sure you'd
want to hear from me.
Oh, that's silly.
We could never
stay mad at you.
Yeah, I've never been one
to hold grudges.
I even forgave the man
who murdered my son.
And although I will never
get over the pain
of what you did to my son,
I forgive you,
because I believe you are sick
and in need of help.
Mr. Griffin, this is
the Office of City Planning.
You requested a variance to
build a hot tub off your garage.
Oh, yeah.
Did I get it?
No.
I will kill your son!
Your son is dead!
I'm so glad there's
no hard feelings.
Listen, Peter, we
should catch up.
Why don't you come over to my
place for a beer or something?
Aw, that sounds great!
Hey, you want me
to pick anything up
on the way over
or no, you're good?
Oh, uh...
I-I guess we could maybe
just order something.
Yeah, I don't have any cash,
but we'll figure it out.
Hey, Peter.
Come on in.
Mi casa es, uh...
I-I don't know Spanish.
Huh, I think half the world
would be surprised to know that.
Hey, nice place here.
This is not too... too...
it's not... it's not too...
not too good.
Yeah, I know it's
nothing fancy,
but, you know, I'm not really
into material possessions.
Geez, this place
is depressing.
Hey, how come you aren't
with your family
during Christmas, anyway?
I can't deal with my family
during the holidays.
And besides, my dad
always spends Christmas
at his time-share in Coral
Gables with his girlfriend.
Great, here comes that couple
with the adult disabled kid.
Hey, can we join you?
I-I'm Ken, this is Pam,
and this right here is Scott.
We really want to thank
you, God, for testing us.
It's been such
a blessing.
Can't wait to see what
that "bigger plan" is.
Well, I can't
tell you that.
But the good news is,
this little guy's
gonna make it to 74.
Oh, look, Jesus, you shouldn't
be alone during Christmas.
And if I remember
correctly,
isn't your birthday
sometime soon, too?
Ah, whatever,
I'm fine.
I'll probably just reheat some
ramen and watch Grey's Anatomy.
No way. I'm not gonna
let my pal Jesus
spend his birthday like that.
Hey, you know what?
I am throwing you
the best birthday party ever.
Are you sure
about that?
Yeah, I'm great
at throwing parties.
I was in charge
of planning Woodstock.
All right, guys, here's
what I'm thinking--
a whole festival
of muddy boobs.
Well, don't you want
to have music?
Oh, yeah.
That's a good way to get
those muddy boobs moving.
All right, you guys, Jesus's
birthday party is gonna be epic.
Hey, since it's
also Christmas,
maybe we could make it,
like, a Christmas theme.
What about
Secret Santa?
That's always fun.
Okay, but five dollar limit.
Why don't we
just say no gifts?
Come on, guys, we don't have to
make such a big thing about it.
It's not like I'm a woman
who's about to turn 30.
You guys, I don't care
what we do for my birthday,
as long as it lasts
the whole week
and is very expensive and
inconvenient for all my friends.
Oh, and I'm gonna
dress like a slut
and be rude to everyone
for no reason.
But, Maya...
I don't care that
your dad's dying,
we're all going to
Montreal for the week.
Wait, wait, hold on.
If we're planning a party,
we haven't even talked about
the most important thing.
A hydration plan for
people who overheat?
It could be as simple
as an ice bath.
No, no, I'm talking
about women.
Oh, yeah, we definitely need
some women there.
Jesus, what kind
of girls do you like?
Women?
Uh, all types,
I guess.
"All types"?
Come on, Jesus.
Even Martin Lawrence when he
used to dress up like Shenehneh?
CLEVELAND:
(laughs) Shenehneh!
No, you know
what I mean.
Uh, like, uh,
hot ladies.
Horny ones who
sex on you.
What?
Yeah, you know.
They come back to your house
and sit on your... butt.
Wait a minute.
Jesus, have you ever
been with a woman?
Are you...
are you a virgin?
(sighs)
Yeah, I am.
How the hell
does that happen?
Well, in high school, my best
friend was this hot prostitute,
and I just kind of got
into the friend zone.
She's all like,
"Oh, there's all these guys
having sex with me for money."
And I'm all like,
"Oh, you deserve better."
And then I die.
Well, sex is
overrated.
Stay out
of this, Joe.
All right, look,
forget the party.
We got a more
important mission now.
Your 2,000-year-long cold streak
is about to come to an end.
What do you mean?
I'm saying, Jesus, we are gonna
help you lose your virginity.
(squeals)
God, I love sex!
All right, me and
the guys are off
to help Jesus lose
his virginity.
Just put it in the oven
for half an hour at 350.
What?
I don't know.
That's what you
always say
when you leave
the house.
Oh, Peter,
just be careful.
Losing your virginity
is a big deal.
I'm sure Jesus doesn't want
some gross quickie.
No, no, no, it's gonna
be nothing like that.
Just some random slut
to maul in a bar
back where the
payphones used to be.
Peter, that's
what I'm talking about.
You're making
this whole thing crude.
It's his first time.
You need to be
more sensitive.
Don't worry, Lois.
I swear, I'll be
sensitive and gentle.
Like the Tasmanian Devil
tucking in his kids.
(soothing Tasmanian Devil
gibbering)
(gibbering)
All right, Jesus,
these speed date nights
are the best way
to meet a lot of chicks fast.
Now go get 'em.
So, where
do you live?
Everywhere, all places.
Hopefully, inside you.
(buzzer sounds)
This is kind of
embarrassing,
but are you okay
with someone who smokes?
Oh, yeah.
A-Are you okay with someone
who wanders the desert,
lecturing people
on how to act?
(buzzer sounds)
So, are you having
a good Friday?
Oh, is that supposed
to be funny?
Shut your mouth, bitch.
(buzzer sounds)
How's the wine?
It's terrific.
That's my blood,
you know.
(buzzer sounds)
Where are you from?
Israel.
(buzzer sounds)
All right, Jesus,
nowadays, everything is done
on the Internet.
All right? So, we got
to get you on Facebook.
Uhp, let me just close
a couple of these windows.
There we go.
Sorry, I was up late last night.
(chuckles)
Had the house to myself.
Sorry. Sorry.
Lot of POV stuff.
Yeah, I like to pretend
it's mine down there
what's doing all the slapping.
Peter, how old
is that girl?
Excuse me, won't you?
Ar... lot of scumbags out today.
Well, no luck getting
Jesus laid yet.
I don't get it.
Jewish guys are supposed
to be swimming in tail.
Peter, Jesus is never gonna find
a woman going about it your way.
I think it's time I had
a little talk with him
so he knows what
a woman really wants.
All right,
knock yourself out.
Don't look! Don't look!
Don't look!
Jesus, I asked you
to lunch
because I think you've
been getting bad advice
about finding
a special someone.
Well, Peter's been
doing his best,
but lately he seems more
focused on marketing
his erotic
Advent calendar.
All right, kids, let's see
what's under Christmas...
Ugh, another puckered anus.
Look, Jesus,
just forget whatever
Peter's been telling you.
You just have
to be yourself
and let a sweet girl
see that side of you.
Well, you're easy to talk to.
I just get all tongue-tied
with other girls.
Plus, being myself
isn't that impressive.
What do you mean?
You're sensitive,
you died for our sins
and ascended into Heaven,
and you got nice skin.
Don't be afraid
to be honest with a girl
and show her who you are.
Wow, thanks, Lois.
That's the second best advice
anyone's ever given me.
I don't know, man.
Jesus Hitler Christ
sounds weird.
So just go with "H"?
Yeah.
All right, guys,
let's not get discouraged, okay?
We just got to be more creative
about getting Jesus laid.
I just tell folks to go down
to the Happy Handy Smile Massage
and get it over with.
I sometimes go down there,
and when they tell me
I'm done, I leave.
Hey, guys. Uh, Peter,
can I talk to you for a sec?
Sure.
Peter, listen.
I've found the woman who I'd
like to lose my virginity to.
It's someone
who understands me
and someone I feel
very close to.
Oh, wow.
Jesus, that's great!
Hey, is it
Carrie Underwood?
Somebody told me you
guys went out once.
Yeah, we did.
But it was a disaster.
Jesus, take the wheel.
What?
I want to kill
these (bleep) cops!
Actually, Peter, I want
my first time to be with...
Lois.
Lois, my partner
at the law firm?
No, Peter. It's your Lois.
Lois Griffin.
What?! I am outraged!
But probably not as outraged
as the ten million
Christians watching.
Please write
to this address quickly.
Maybe we can both stop
these Hollywood Jew writers
from wrecking my marriage
and your religion.
You want to lose your
virginity to Lois?!
No way!
Look, Peter, I know
it's a lot to ask.
But if it wasn't okay,
I wouldn't suggest it.
Well, you make
a good point.
But this is my wife
you're talking about!
Please, Peter?
I just know Lois would
make my first experience
as special and memorable
as it should be.
Plus, I can make it
worth your while.
After all, I'm Jesus.
I could give you
anything you want.
Anything?
Like... like anything
in the universe?
Absolutely.
Brookstone massage chair.
Really?
Are-are you sure?
Yup. Never been more sure
of anything in my life.
Well, except one thing.
Good evening, sir.
Would you like to
hear our specials?
No! Pizza!
Let me get
this straight.
You want me to have
sex with another man?
Oh, not just any man, Lois.
This is Jesus
we're talking about.
He's a savior.
He could even save
our marriage.
Why? What's wrong
with our marriage?
"What's wrong
with our marriage?"
You're sitting around, talking
about sleeping with other guys!
Peter, this was
your idea!
Lois, let's not play
the blame game.
Clearly, there's been a lot
of cheating on both sides,
but the point is
where do we go from here?
Huh, I don't know.
Sleeping with Jesus
just feels wrong.
Doesn't the Bible say not to
covet thy neighbor's wife?
Oh, come on, Lois,
the Bible's
just a bunch
of general guidelines.
None of the commandments
are written in stone.
You're really
okay with this?
Of course.
Look, there really is
no downside to this.
It's one of those things that
seems bad, but really is good.
Like that fracking company
we let drill in the backyard.
Well, I guess
it is kind of an honor
that out of all the people
in the world,
Jesus chose me.
I mean, he could've had anyone.
Elizabeth Perkins, Patricia
Richardson, Katey Sagal...
Yeah! I-I mean, maybe not them,
but somebody else.
And-and the Son of God's
first time should be special.
Even divine.
Maybe I'd actually be
doing a good thing.
You sure about
this, Peter?
You bet.
As sure as I was
when I created Lady Gaga.
All right, listen, fella,
your game is confusion.
Zip! Zam! Zoop!
Nobody gets a straight
look at nothing!
Boy, this must be
killing you.
You're an atheist,
and the one guy
you don't believe in
is getting to bang
the woman of your dreams.
You know what? I don't have
to sit here and take this.
I'm out of here.
Can-can you let me outside?
(doorbell rings)
Hi, Peter.
Well, hello, young man.
Don't you look nice?
She's almost ready.
♪ There she goes ♪
♪ There she goes again ♪
♪ Pulsing through my veins ♪
♪ And I just can't contain... ♪
I'm sorry, I was just
coming down the stairs
at the same time.
Wow, Mom.
You look beautiful.
Well, we know he's circumcised,
so she won't have to deal
with that nonsense.
Oh, and don't worry
about not hittinbottom.
I've only grazed it once and
that was with a running start.
Hey, Jerome, give me
another Pawtucket Pat.
I'll take it over here
on my Brookstone massage chair.
That's a nice
chair, Peter.
Hey, do you think if I let
Jesus sleep with Bonnie,
he'd give me back
the use of my legs?
Joe, I don't speak for Jesus.
I just get him trim.
Now to take this thing
out for a spin.
(chair vibrating)
(sighs)
(birds squawking)
Ah, time for a relaxing,
sponsored daydream.
Oh, Jesus!
Jesus! Jesus!
(screams)
God, I love
massage chairs.
Are you in one, too?
Yes, but it's horrible!
It was bought for me by Jesus,
but now he's doing my wife!
Oh. I'm just trying
mine out in the store.
Guys! I think I might've
made a terrible mistake
with this whole
Lois and Jesus thing!
I don't blame you, Peter.
I always thought it was
sort of a strange choice
to let Jesus have
relations with your wife.
I'm sorry, did you say Jesus
is sleeping with your wife?
Great, now everybody knows
my wife is taking
Jesus's virginity.
Listen, pal,
Jesus ain't no virgin.
He did the same thing
to me last Christmas.
He what?!
Yeah, Jesus did
the same thing
to my wife
Christmas before last
and my buddy's wife
the year before that.
What the hell?
But he's so lonely.
Nah, he just acts lonely
and lies about being a virgin
so he can get with guys' wives.
Did he show you
that sad little apartment?
He doesn't really live there.
He just uses it to store art
he bought on cruises.
Oh, my God, what have I done?!
Peter, maybe there's still time!
Maybe you can stop them!
Where are they?
They're at the Barrington Hotel!
Let's go, guys!
I just ordered nachos,
but good luck, Peter.
Now for a slippy, no-boots run
through the snow to my car.
(gasping)
(screams) Aw, crap!
I just pulled
a thousand muscles!
(grunting)
(screams)
Ow! That was a loud crack!
Ah, yeah, that was all bone!
Oh! Aw! Son of a whore!
Oh, this is bad.
This is real bad.
I'm not gonna go
to the doctor though.
(ignition sputters)
Damn it!
(tires screech)
Get out!
I need this car!
What are you, a cop?
No! Jesus is about to
have sex with my wife!
Oh, then here! Take it!
Get out!
I need this car!
So do I!
Jesus Christ is about
to have sex with my wife!
Lenny Kravitz is about
to have sex with my daughter!
Oh! Oh, my God!
Here, take the car!
Take the car!
Get out of here!
What are you doing?!
Go, go, go!
Hey, kid, I need
that toboggan!
Jesus Christ is gonna
have sex with my wife!
Um, okay.
And I need
your little hat.
And those Spider-Man mittens--
I'll need those, too.
And what's in
your pockets?
A rabbit's foot, a penknife,
a bottle cap, a compass...
All of it, all of it.
(tires screeching)
Aw, crap. I'm out of hill.
You there! Boy!
What does that sign say?
I ain't much
for book reading, sir.
But I seen our Lord and Savior
bring a lady in there
for a Christmas rodgering,
I did.
You're a good boy.
Here's a goose.
(goose honks)
What room is Jesus in?
What room is
Lenny Kravitz in?
Aw, you were coming here, too?
We could've carpooled.
(elevator bell dings)
Lois! Lois!
You son of a bitch!
What have you done
to my marriage?!
Peter?
Lois, don't do this!
I think I had, like,
a Christmas miracle.
I realized I don't
want other people
humping my wife
for a chair.
It's okay, Peter.
Nothing happened.
It didn't?
No, I couldn't
sleep with him.
Not that I wasn't tempted.
He put actual strawberries
in a glass of champagne,
which was about the classiest,
sexiest thing I'd ever seen.
But...
I couldn't go through with it.
Our marriage is
too important to me.
I love you, Lois.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
But you!
You're a liar, Jesus!
Bravo, Peter, Lois.
Seems like you folks learned
the lesson I intended.
What lesson?
Oh, you know, uh...
that, uh, this holiest
of days is about,
uh, appreciating...
our loved ones and, uh,
resisting... temptation.
Oh, so it was a test.
Like when your father told
Abraham to sacrifice Isaac?
Yes! That!
That's exactly right!
Uh, well, I can see
my work here is done.
Well taught, Jesus.
Well taught.
Yeah, I guess.
Who cares?
I'm not even real.
Merry Christmas.
Well, Lois, I'm sure glad
you didn't have sex
with the Messiah.
Me, too, Peter.
Now let's open
your presents, kids.
Oh, Rupert, you're
such a sneak.
I wonder what it is.
Oh. A Joni Mitchell CD.
"To continue your
emotional education."
That's great.
(chuckles)
That's really great.
Could you excuse me
for just one moment?
♪ I've looked at clouds
from both sides now... ♪
Who did he buy
the necklace for?
I'm gonna let that teddy bear
go all the way.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru